[
    {
        "question":"What does HTML stand for?",
        "answer-1":"Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "answer-2":"High Tech Multimedia Language",
        "answer-3":"Hyper Transfer Markup Language",
        "answer-4":"Home Tool Markup Language",
        "answer":"Hyper Text Markup Language"
    },
    {
        "question":" Which HTML tag is used for creating a hyperlink?",
        "answer-1":"<link>",
        "answer-2":"<a>",
        "answer-3":"<hlink>",
        "answer-4":"<hyper>",
        "answer":"<a>"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which HTML element is used to define the structure of an HTML document?",
        "answer-1":"<body>",
        "answer-2":"<head>",
        "answer-3":"<html>",
        "answer-4":"<structure>",
        "answer":"<html>"
    },
    {
        "question":"What does the <img> tag stand for in HTML?",
        "answer-1":"Image",
        "answer-2":"Insert",
        "answer-3":"Inline",
        "answer-4":"Input",
        "answer":"Image"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which HTML tag is used for creating an unordered list?",
        "answer-1":"<list>",
        "answer-2":"<ul>",
        "answer-3":"<ol>",
        "answer-4":"<li>",
        "answer":"<ul>"
    },
    {
        "question":" Which HTML tag is used for creating a line break?",
        "answer-1":"<br>",
        "answer-2":"<lb>",
        "answer-3":"<linebreak>",
        "answer-4":"<newline>",
        "answer":"<br>"
    },
    {
        "question":"In HTML, which tag is used to define the structure of a table?",
        "answer-1":"<row>",
        "answer-2":"<table>",
        "answer-3":"<grid>",
        "answer-4":"<struct>",
        "answer":"<table>"
    },
    {
        "question":"What is the purpose of the <meta> tag in HTML?",
        "answer-1":"To create metadata for search engines",
        "answer-2":"To define a paragraph",
        "answer-3":"InlTo display imagesine",
        "answer-4":"To insert JavaScript code",
        "answer":"To create metadata for search engines"
    },
    {
        "question":"Which HTML tag is used for defining the largest heading?",
        "answer-1":"<heading1>",
        "answer-2":"<h1>",
        "answer-3":"<header>",
        "answer-4":"<big>",
        "answer":"<h1>"
    },
    {
        "question":"What does CSS stand for in the context of web development?",
        "answer-1":"Computer System Styles",
        "answer-2":"Cascading Style Sheets",
        "answer-3":"Colorful Style Selection",
        "answer-4":"Code Structure and Syntax",
        "answer":"Cascading Style Sheets"
    }
]
